I am Arwen - I've come to help you.
Hear my voice...
Come back to the light.
Stay with the Hobbits -
I'll send horses for you.
I'm the faster rider - I'll take him
The Road is too dangerous.
If I can get across the river...
...the power of my people
will protect him.
The Shadow does not hold sway yet.
Not over you... not over me.
Do you remember when we first met?
I thought I had strayed into a dream.
Long years have passed.
You did not have the cares you carry now.
Do you remember what I told you?
Sit down, Legolas.
She wanted to protect her child...
she thought in Rivendell
you would be safe.
Welcome Legolas, son of Thranduil.
Our Fellowship stands in your debt.
Aragorn of the Dunedain...
you are known to us.
You are being tracked.
For her love,
I fear the grace of Arwen Evenstar
will diminish.
I would have her leave these shores,
and be with her people.
I would have her take the ship to Valinor.
Farewell.
There is much you have yet to do.
We shall not meet again...
Elessar.
[English]