Something’s out there.
What do you see?
Your name is kingly.
You told me once...
this day would come.
This is not the end...it is the beginning.
You must go with Frodo.
That is your path.
My path is hidden from me.
It is already laid before your feet.
You cannot falter now.
If you trust nothing else...
trust this...
trust us.
Is this how you would take your leave?
Did you think you could slip away at
first light - unnoticed?
I will not be coming back.
You underestimate your skill in battle.
You will come back.
It is not of death in battle that I speak.
What do you speak of?
You have a chance for another life...
away from war...grief...despair.
It is time.
The ships are leaving for Valinor.
Go now... before it is too late.
Do I not also have your love?
You have my love, father.
You're late.
And they should be...
Three hundred... against ten thousand!
They have more hope of defending
themselves here than at Edoras...
They cannot win this fight.
They are all going to die!
There is nothing to forgive, Legolas.
Show them no mercy...
for you shall receive none!
HOLD!
Prepare to fire!
Their armour is weak at the neck...
and beneath the arm.
Release Arrows!
Ladders!
Bring him down, Legolas!
Kill him!
Charge!
To the Keep!
Pull back to the Keep!